export type GameFieldTypes = {
    id: number
    question: string
    answer: string
    buttonText: string
}[]

let game_id = 0

export const howWellDoYouKnowMom = [
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "What city was she born?",
        answer: "Everett, WA",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "What's her ultimate pregnancy craving?",
        answer: "Ice cream",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "What is her favorite movie?",
        answer: "Sound of Music",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "What is her favorite color?",
        answer: "Pink",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "What is her middle name?",
        answer: "Michelle",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Where was her first job?",
        answer: "Dairy Queen",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "What is her favorite dessert?",
        answer: "Brownie with Ice Cream",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "What is her favorite hobby?",
        answer: "Weight Lifting",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "What is her favorite animal?",
        answer: "Dog",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "What is her biggest fear?",
        answer: "Being alone",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "What is her favorite vacation spot?",
        answer: "The beach",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "What was the name of her first pet?",
        answer: "Cassie the Cat",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "What is her favorite season?",
        answer: "Winter",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "What is her favorite type of cuisine?",
        answer: "Italian",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "What is her favorite flower?",
        answer: "Yellow Dragonsnap",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "What was her favorite subject in school?",
        answer: "Choir/Music",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "What is her dream job?",
        answer: "Fitness Influencer",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "What is her favorite holiday?",
        answer: "Christmas",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "What is her favorite alcoholic drink?",
        answer: "Raspberry Cosmopolitan",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "What is her go-to form of self care?",
        answer: "Bath",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "How many kids does she want?",
        answer: "One",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "When is her due date?",
        answer: "July 27th, 2024",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "What is her birthday?",
        answer: "October 5th, 1996",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    }
]

export const priceIsRightGame: GameFieldTypes = [
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a pack of diapers (Size 1, 100 count)?",
        answer: "$25.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a baby stroller?",
        answer: "$149.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a baby crib?",
        answer: "$299.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a baby monitor?",
        answer: "$59.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a pack of baby wipes (500 count)?",
        answer: "$15.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a baby high chair?",
        answer: "$89.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a baby bottle set (6 bottles)?",
        answer: "$24.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a baby car seat?",
        answer: "$199.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a baby swing?",
        answer: "$129.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a baby bathtub?",
        answer: "$29.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a baby carrier?",
        answer: "$49.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a baby bouncer?",
        answer: "$69.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a baby play mat?",
        answer: "$39.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a pack of baby pacifiers (3 count)?",
        answer: "$8.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a baby thermometer?",
        answer: "$19.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a baby changing table?",
        answer: "$99.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a baby diaper bag?",
        answer: "$45.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a baby walker?",
        answer: "$59.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a baby food maker?",
        answer: "$79.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a baby humidifier?",
        answer: "$49.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a baby safety gate?",
        answer: "$34.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a baby teething toy?",
        answer: "$12.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a baby sleep sack?",
        answer: "$29.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a baby playpen?",
        answer: "$89.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Price of a baby rocking chair?",
        answer: "$159.99",
        buttonText: "Answer"
    }
]

const totalPrice = priceIsRightGame.reduce((total, item) => {
    const price = parseFloat(item.answer.replace('$', ''))
    return total + price
}, 0)

priceIsRightGame.push({
    id: game_id++,
    question: "Grand Total",
    answer: `$${totalPrice.toFixed(2)}`,
    buttonText: " See Total"
})

export const guessWhichParentGame: GameFieldTypes = [
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who loves to cook more?",
        answer: "Dad",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who is more likely to take a nap?",
        answer: "Mom",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who is better at fixing things around the house?",
        answer: "Dad",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who enjoys reading books more?",
        answer: "Mom",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who has a sweeter tooth?",
        answer: "Mom",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who is more likely to plan a family trip?",
        answer: "Dad",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who is better at remembering important dates?",
        answer: "Mom",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who has a better sense of humor?",
        answer: "Dad",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who is more organized?",
        answer: "Mom",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who is a better dancer?",
        answer: "Dad",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who is more likely to try new foods?",
        answer: "Dad",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who is more tech-savvy?",
        answer: "Dad",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who wakes up earlier?",
        answer: "Dad",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who is more likely to binge-watch a TV series?",
        answer: "Mom",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who is more likely to take the kids to the park?",
        answer: "Dad",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who spends more time on social media?",
        answer: "Mom",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who is more likely to sing along to the radio?",
        answer: "Dad",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who is more likely to play video games?",
        answer: "Dad",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who is more adventurous?",
        answer: "Dad",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who is more likely to stay up late?",
        answer: "Dad",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who is better at telling stories?",
        answer: "Mom",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who is more likely to volunteer for kids school activities?",
        answer: "Mom",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who is better at keeping secrets?",
        answer: "Dad",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who is more likely to win at board games?",
        answer: "Dad",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who will cry the most at birth?",
        answer: "Mom",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who will change the first diaper blowout?",
        answer: "Dad",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who will use the most baby talk?",
        answer: "Dad",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who will worry more?",
        answer: "Mom",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who will be the better burper?",
        answer: "Mom",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who will have the better lullaby voice?",
        answer: "Mom",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who will actually sleep when the baby sleeps?",
        answer: "Mom",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who will put a pacifier in their mouth to clean it after it falls on the floor?",
        answer: "Mom",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    },
    {
        id: game_id++,
        question: "Who will do the smell test to check if the baby has pooped?",
        answer: "Dad",
        buttonText: "Guess"
    }
]